{"results": [{"question": "When did Airbnb go public, what was the price per share", "answer": {"query": "When did Airbnb go public, what was the price per share", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Why did Wimdu unlike Airbnb not take off?", "answer": {"query": "Why did Wimdu unlike Airbnb not take off?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Why does market fragmentation work for airline industry but could't work for Airbnb", "answer": {"query": "Why does market fragmentation work for airline industry but could't work for Airbnb", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How many hot dogs does Costco currently sell per year?", "answer": {"query": "How many hot dogs does Costco currently sell per year?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What store was created as \"the price club of hardware stores\"?", "answer": {"query": "What store was created as \"the price club of hardware stores\"?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How long did it take for Costco to generate 1 billion dollars in revenue?", "answer": {"query": "How long did it take for Costco to generate 1 billion dollars in revenue?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the New Look?", "answer": {"query": "What is the New Look?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How much money did the Arnaut family offer to buy out the Boussac group?", "answer": null, "cypher_query": null, "status": "error", "error": "{code: Neo.ClientError.Statement.SyntaxError} {message: Variable `amount` not defined (line 1, column 95 (offset: 94))\n\"MATCH (:Family {name: \"Arnaut\"})-[:OFFERED_TO_BUY]->(:Company {name: \"Boussac group\"}) RETURN amount\"\n                                                                                               ^}"}, {"question": "What is American Crown Jewel?", "answer": {"query": "What is American Crown Jewel?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "According to Information Theory, what is the importance of knowing what message your sender is trying to convey?", "answer": {"query": "According to Information Theory, what is the importance of knowing what message your sender is trying to convey?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Compare the impact on Qualcomm between the two Jacobs.", "answer": {"query": "Compare the impact on Qualcomm between the two Jacobs.", "result": "Paul Jacobs has had a greater impact on Qualcomm compared to Irwin Jacobs."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the Scandinavian connection to Qualcomm's early rise?", "answer": {"query": "What is the Scandinavian connection to Qualcomm's early rise?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "When did AWS formed and who first head of AWS techincally?", "answer": {"query": "When did AWS formed and who first head of AWS techincally?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was the final words by Amazon CTO Werner Vogels in Quora Post in 2011?", "answer": {"query": "What was the final words by Amazon CTO Werner Vogels in Quora Post in 2011?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What boots and jacket we often see Jeff Bezos in ?", "answer": {"query": "What boots and jacket we often see Jeff Bezos in ?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Where is Blue Origins operations are based in?", "answer": {"query": "Where is Blue Origins operations are based in?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Which was one of the first free email services?", "answer": {"query": "Which was one of the first free email services?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "When was the summit that eventually lead to the creation of Visa?", "answer": {"query": "When was the summit that eventually lead to the creation of Visa?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is Visa's net income margin and is there a company with a better margin?", "answer": {"query": "What is Visa's net income margin and is there a company with a better margin?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Visa is the global sponsor of what?", "answer": {"query": "Visa is the global sponsor of what?", "result": "Visa is the global sponsor of the Olympics."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "In 1976, Steve Jobs along with Steve Wozniak created the game, Breakout, for Atari and Nolan Bushnell. Three industries were born concurrent with the creation of this game. What where they?", "answer": {"query": "In 1976, Steve Jobs along with Steve Wozniak created the game, Breakout, for Atari and Nolan Bushnell. Three industries were born concurrent with the creation of this game. What where they?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What does Nintendo mean?", "answer": null, "cypher_query": null, "status": "error", "error": "{code: Neo.ClientError.Statement.SyntaxError} {message: Invalid input 'I': expected 'FOREACH', 'ALTER', 'ORDER BY', 'CALL', 'USING PERIODIC COMMIT', 'CREATE', 'LOAD CSV', 'START DATABASE', 'STOP DATABASE', 'DEALLOCATE', 'DELETE', 'DENY', 'DETACH', 'DROP', 'DRYRUN', 'FINISH', 'GRANT', 'INSERT', 'LIMIT', 'MATCH', 'MERGE', 'NODETACH', 'OFFSET', 'OPTIONAL', 'REALLOCATE', 'REMOVE', 'RENAME', 'RETURN', 'REVOKE', 'ENABLE SERVER', 'SET', 'SHOW', 'SKIP', 'TERMINATE', 'UNWIND', 'USE' or 'WITH' (line 1, column 1 (offset: 0))\n\"I'm sorry, but I can't provide the requested information.\"\n ^}"}, {"question": "What was a key strength of Hiroshi Yamauchi? This is something that he was just good at. ", "answer": {"query": "What was a key strength of Hiroshi Yamauchi? This is something that he was just good at. ", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What are the 3 interrelated things that make Renaissance Technologies unique from other investment firms with similar commodities (smartest people with the best data and infrastructure), such as Citadel, DE Saw, Two Sigma, and Jane Street?", "answer": {"query": "What are the 3 interrelated things that make Renaissance Technologies unique from other investment firms with similar commodities (smartest people with the best data and infrastructure), such as Citadel, DE Saw, Two Sigma, and Jane Street?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What series of philosophical arguments presented by an ancient Greek philosopher does Jim Simons, the founder of Renaissance Technologies, learn about as a 4-year-old that sparks his interest in math?", "answer": {"query": "What series of philosophical arguments presented by an ancient Greek philosopher does Jim Simons, the founder of Renaissance Technologies, learn about as a 4-year-old that sparks his interest in math?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "In the year 2000, when the tech bubble bursts and the market is down big, what was the Medallion Fund's % gross returns?", "answer": {"query": "In the year 2000, when the tech bubble bursts and the market is down big, what was the Medallion Fund's % gross returns?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "who was the first rocket engine engineer in spacex", "answer": {"query": "who was the first rocket engine engineer in spacex", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "can you tell me total number of people working in Spacex", "answer": {"query": "can you tell me total number of people working in Spacex", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the cost of rocket travel based on the materials?", "answer": {"query": "What is the cost of rocket travel based on the materials?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "what is the idea about mars oasis", "answer": {"query": "what is the idea about mars oasis", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was Elon Musk\ufffds initial investment in SpaceX?", "answer": {"query": "What was Elon Musk\ufffds initial investment in SpaceX?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How is Jim Weber's strategic focus influence the revitalization of Brooks Running?", "answer": {"query": "How is Jim Weber's strategic focus influence the revitalization of Brooks Running?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How did Brooks Running approach to market segmentation give it a competitive advantage?", "answer": {"query": "How did Brooks Running approach to market segmentation give it a competitive advantage?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was the patent Heddy developed? Was it publicly available?", "answer": {"query": "What was the patent Heddy developed? Was it publicly available?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Why were patents developed by Heddy had 88 frequency hops ?", "answer": {"query": "Why were patents developed by Heddy had 88 frequency hops ?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was the role of Trump administration on the takeover of Broadcomm over Qualcomm and why the decision was made?", "answer": {"query": "What was the role of Trump administration on the takeover of Broadcomm over Qualcomm and why the decision was made?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "what is one decision Porsche made to improve business that went against industry norm?", "answer": {"query": "what is one decision Porsche made to improve business that went against industry norm?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What city owns 20% of volkswagen and why", "answer": {"query": "What city owns 20% of volkswagen and why", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What's Startup Garage at Stanford's GSB?", "answer": {"query": "What's Startup Garage at Stanford's GSB?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Who is the owner of the shop that ispired the idea behind the doordash app?", "answer": {"query": "Who is the owner of the shop that ispired the idea behind the doordash app?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Where was the first customer of paloaltodelivery.com working at? what was he doing at Stanford?", "answer": {"query": "Where was the first customer of paloaltodelivery.com working at? what was he doing at Stanford?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What seminar did Sam Walton enroll himself in in poughkeepsie New York", "answer": {"query": "What seminar did Sam Walton enroll himself in in poughkeepsie New York", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What Percentage of Rent to Sales did Sam Waltons first Ben Franklin cost", "answer": {"query": "What Percentage of Rent to Sales did Sam Waltons first Ben Franklin cost", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How much top line revenue % did walmart see a year after their IPO 1972", "answer": {"query": "How much top line revenue % did walmart see a year after their IPO 1972", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "why did Nvidia use a startup Foundry emulation software to produce their chips at some point", "answer": {"query": "why did Nvidia use a startup Foundry emulation software to produce their chips at some point", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What did Nvidia call its first graphics card", "answer": {"query": "What did Nvidia call its first graphics card", "result": "Nvidia called its first graphics cards Grace Cpu Processor, Hopper Gpu, and Lovelace Gpu."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Why did Jensen decide to write and send a letter through a physical address to Morris of TSMC", "answer": {"query": "Why did Jensen decide to write and send a letter through a physical address to Morris of TSMC", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was Peloton original price", "answer": {"query": "What was Peloton original price", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How much stock did John Foley had in Peloton in 2022", "answer": {"query": "How much stock did John Foley had in Peloton in 2022", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What percentage of NBA league revenue since 1983 has been contractually going to players?", "answer": {"query": "What percentage of NBA league revenue since 1983 has been contractually going to players?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the analogy in the Podcast for \"Bitcoin is calculator, let's build a computer\"?", "answer": {"query": "What is the analogy in the Podcast for \"Bitcoin is calculator, let's build a computer\"?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the connection to Vitalik to the year 1994 and what was his parent's condition and Russia during the time?", "answer": {"query": "What is the connection to Vitalik to the year 1994 and what was his parent's condition and Russia during the time?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was argument before Vtalik's presentation in Miami?", "answer": {"query": "What was argument before Vtalik's presentation in Miami?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "what was the worst stock price percentage down in a day for NVIDIA ?", "answer": {"query": "what was the worst stock price percentage down in a day for NVIDIA ?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "In 2012, What is the  competition against imageNet Database and what was the error rate compared to others & who won the competition?", "answer": {"query": "In 2012, What is the  competition against imageNet Database and what was the error rate compared to others & who won the competition?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is NVIDIA free cash flow in billions  every year? ", "answer": {"query": "What is NVIDIA free cash flow in billions  every year? ", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is the difference between recurrent neural networks and convolutional neural networks?", "answer": null, "cypher_query": null, "status": "error", "error": "{code: Neo.ClientError.Statement.SyntaxError} {message: Invalid input 'I': expected 'FOREACH', 'ALTER', 'ORDER BY', 'CALL', 'USING PERIODIC COMMIT', 'CREATE', 'LOAD CSV', 'START DATABASE', 'STOP DATABASE', 'DEALLOCATE', 'DELETE', 'DENY', 'DETACH', 'DROP', 'DRYRUN', 'FINISH', 'GRANT', 'INSERT', 'LIMIT', 'MATCH', 'MERGE', 'NODETACH', 'OFFSET', 'OPTIONAL', 'REALLOCATE', 'REMOVE', 'RENAME', 'RETURN', 'REVOKE', 'ENABLE SERVER', 'SET', 'SHOW', 'SKIP', 'TERMINATE', 'UNWIND', 'USE' or 'WITH' (line 1, column 1 (offset: 0))\n\"I'm sorry, but I can't provide an answer to that question.\"\n ^}"}, {"question": "What did Jensen Huang say in the Stratechery interview in March 2023 about the year 2022?", "answer": {"query": "What did Jensen Huang say in the Stratechery interview in March 2023 about the year 2022?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is CUDA's most unique feature?", "answer": null, "cypher_query": null, "status": "error", "error": "{code: Neo.ClientError.Statement.SyntaxError} {message: Invalid input 'I': expected 'FOREACH', 'ALTER', 'ORDER BY', 'CALL', 'USING PERIODIC COMMIT', 'CREATE', 'LOAD CSV', 'START DATABASE', 'STOP DATABASE', 'DEALLOCATE', 'DELETE', 'DENY', 'DETACH', 'DROP', 'DRYRUN', 'FINISH', 'GRANT', 'INSERT', 'LIMIT', 'MATCH', 'MERGE', 'NODETACH', 'OFFSET', 'OPTIONAL', 'REALLOCATE', 'REMOVE', 'RENAME', 'RETURN', 'REVOKE', 'ENABLE SERVER', 'SET', 'SHOW', 'SKIP', 'TERMINATE', 'UNWIND', 'USE' or 'WITH' (line 1, column 1 (offset: 0))\n\"I'm sorry, but I can't provide the requested information.\"\n ^}"}, {"question": "Where did the issuance of the first banknotes originate?", "answer": {"query": "Where did the issuance of the first banknotes originate?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "what happen on 2013 in relation to bitcoin ", "answer": {"query": "what happen on 2013 in relation to bitcoin ", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "does bitcoin have a higher appreciation per year as compared to gold?", "answer": {"query": "does bitcoin have a higher appreciation per year as compared to gold?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "how did Winklevoss brother changed the bitcoin market ", "answer": {"query": "how did Winklevoss brother changed the bitcoin market ", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "In February 1967, Warren Buffet decide to transform Berkshire into an insurance company. How much time did it take for Warrne Buffet to work out on a deal?", "answer": {"query": "In February 1967, Warren Buffet decide to transform Berkshire into an insurance company. How much time did it take for Warrne Buffet to work out on a deal?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What is Warren Buffet net worth after working at Graham-Newman for two years?", "answer": {"query": "What is Warren Buffet net worth after working at Graham-Newman for two years?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "On which day of the week did Warren Buffet talked with Lorimer and for how long?", "answer": {"query": "On which day of the week did Warren Buffet talked with Lorimer and for how long?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "Which company, in addition to Facebook and Google, showed interest in WhatsApp?", "answer": {"query": "Which company, in addition to Facebook and Google, showed interest in WhatsApp?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "During high school year, which online security community Jan Koum was part of? ", "answer": {"query": "During high school year, which online security community Jan Koum was part of? ", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What business strategies did Jan used to increase the popularity of the WhatsApp product?", "answer": {"query": "What business strategies did Jan used to increase the popularity of the WhatsApp product?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What company did Disney invest in and eventually purchase for the technology to enable their streaming services platform?", "answer": {"query": "What company did Disney invest in and eventually purchase for the technology to enable their streaming services platform?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was the result of the shareholder no confidence bid against Bob Eisner after the failed Disney takeover bid by Comcast?", "answer": {"query": "What was the result of the shareholder no confidence bid against Bob Eisner after the failed Disney takeover bid by Comcast?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What position did Bob Eisner have and in what company when Disney acquired it?", "answer": {"query": "What position did Bob Eisner have and in what company when Disney acquired it?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What did Jeffrey Skilling say to the dean of Harvard Business School during his entrance interview?", "answer": {"query": "What did Jeffrey Skilling say to the dean of Harvard Business School during his entrance interview?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was the singular condition that Jeffrey Skilling requested before joining Enron?", "answer": {"query": "What was the singular condition that Jeffrey Skilling requested before joining Enron?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What historic event took investigative pressure off of Enron before its stock collapsed?", "answer": {"query": "What historic event took investigative pressure off of Enron before its stock collapsed?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "How did Enron remove investments from its accounting books?", "answer": {"query": "How did Enron remove investments from its accounting books?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "The fall of Enron is similar to what other bankruptcy from 2022?", "answer": {"query": "The fall of Enron is similar to what other bankruptcy from 2022?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What metrics did FTX judge itself by?", "answer": {"query": "What metrics did FTX judge itself by?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "When was Trip Hawkins exposed to Computers?", "answer": {"query": "When was Trip Hawkins exposed to Computers?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}, {"question": "What was Trip Hawkins favorite game growing up?", "answer": {"query": "What was Trip Hawkins favorite game growing up?", "result": "I don't know the answer."}, "cypher_query": null, "status": "success"}], "processed_questions": ["When did Airbnb go public, what was the price per share", "Why did Wimdu unlike Airbnb not take off?", "Why does market fragmentation work for airline industry but could't work for Airbnb", "How many hot dogs does Costco currently sell per year?", "What store was created as \"the price club of hardware stores\"?", "How long did it take for Costco to generate 1 billion dollars in revenue?", "What is the New Look?", "What is American Crown Jewel?", "According to Information Theory, what is the importance of knowing what message your sender is trying to convey?", "Compare the impact on Qualcomm between the two Jacobs.", "What is the Scandinavian connection to Qualcomm's early rise?", "When did AWS formed and who first head of AWS techincally?", "What was the final words by Amazon CTO Werner Vogels in Quora Post in 2011?", "What boots and jacket we often see Jeff Bezos in ?", "Where is Blue Origins operations are based in?", "Which was one of the first free email services?", "When was the summit that eventually lead to the creation of Visa?", "What is Visa's net income margin and is there a company with a better margin?", "Visa is the global sponsor of what?", "In 1976, Steve Jobs along with Steve Wozniak created the game, Breakout, for Atari and Nolan Bushnell. Three industries were born concurrent with the creation of this game. What where they?", "What was a key strength of Hiroshi Yamauchi? This is something that he was just good at. ", "What are the 3 interrelated things that make Renaissance Technologies unique from other investment firms with similar commodities (smartest people with the best data and infrastructure), such as Citadel, DE Saw, Two Sigma, and Jane Street?", "What series of philosophical arguments presented by an ancient Greek philosopher does Jim Simons, the founder of Renaissance Technologies, learn about as a 4-year-old that sparks his interest in math?", "In the year 2000, when the tech bubble bursts and the market is down big, what was the Medallion Fund's % gross returns?", "who was the first rocket engine engineer in spacex", "can you tell me total number of people working in Spacex", "What is the cost of rocket travel based on the materials?", "what is the idea about mars oasis", "What was Elon Musk\ufffds initial investment in SpaceX?", "How is Jim Weber's strategic focus influence the revitalization of Brooks Running?", "How did Brooks Running approach to market segmentation give it a competitive advantage?", "What was the patent Heddy developed? Was it publicly available?", "Why were patents developed by Heddy had 88 frequency hops ?", "What was the role of Trump administration on the takeover of Broadcomm over Qualcomm and why the decision was made?", "what is one decision Porsche made to improve business that went against industry norm?", "What city owns 20% of volkswagen and why", "What's Startup Garage at Stanford's GSB?", "Who is the owner of the shop that ispired the idea behind the doordash app?", "Where was the first customer of paloaltodelivery.com working at? what was he doing at Stanford?", "What seminar did Sam Walton enroll himself in in poughkeepsie New York", "What Percentage of Rent to Sales did Sam Waltons first Ben Franklin cost", "How much top line revenue % did walmart see a year after their IPO 1972", "why did Nvidia use a startup Foundry emulation software to produce their chips at some point", "What did Nvidia call its first graphics card", "Why did Jensen decide to write and send a letter through a physical address to Morris of TSMC", "What was Peloton original price", "How much stock did John Foley had in Peloton in 2022", "What percentage of NBA league revenue since 1983 has been contractually going to players?", "What is the analogy in the Podcast for \"Bitcoin is calculator, let's build a computer\"?", "What is the connection to Vitalik to the year 1994 and what was his parent's condition and Russia during the time?", "What was argument before Vtalik's presentation in Miami?", "what was the worst stock price percentage down in a day for NVIDIA ?", "In 2012, What is the  competition against imageNet Database and what was the error rate compared to others & who won the competition?", "What is NVIDIA free cash flow in billions  every year? ", "What did Jensen Huang say in the Stratechery interview in March 2023 about the year 2022?", "Where did the issuance of the first banknotes originate?", "what happen on 2013 in relation to bitcoin ", "does bitcoin have a higher appreciation per year as compared to gold?", "how did Winklevoss brother changed the bitcoin market ", "In February 1967, Warren Buffet decide to transform Berkshire into an insurance company. How much time did it take for Warrne Buffet to work out on a deal?", "What is Warren Buffet net worth after working at Graham-Newman for two years?", "On which day of the week did Warren Buffet talked with Lorimer and for how long?", "Which company, in addition to Facebook and Google, showed interest in WhatsApp?", "During high school year, which online security community Jan Koum was part of? ", "What business strategies did Jan used to increase the popularity of the WhatsApp product?", "What company did Disney invest in and eventually purchase for the technology to enable their streaming services platform?", "What was the result of the shareholder no confidence bid against Bob Eisner after the failed Disney takeover bid by Comcast?", "What position did Bob Eisner have and in what company when Disney acquired it?", "What did Jeffrey Skilling say to the dean of Harvard Business School during his entrance interview?", "What was the singular condition that Jeffrey Skilling requested before joining Enron?", "What historic event took investigative pressure off of Enron before its stock collapsed?", "How did Enron remove investments from its accounting books?", "The fall of Enron is similar to what other bankruptcy from 2022?", "What metrics did FTX judge itself by?", "When was Trip Hawkins exposed to Computers?", "What was Trip Hawkins favorite game growing up?"]}